

TECHNOLOGIES & LANGAGES

HTML/CSS/JS
PHP/SYMFONY 4
NODEJS/MONGODB/EXPRESS
NOSQL/SQL
GRAPHQL/APOLLO
REACTJS/REDUX
ANGULAR 7
IONIC 3
ANDROID
SWIFT/ XCODE
JAVA/JEE
GIT/GITHUB
LINUX
WEB SCRAPING
UI/UX

PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork
Stress management
Time management
Solution oriented
Agile method (SCRUM)
Public speaking

C#/ASP.NET MVC

CONTACT

T: +216 53 451 615 E: bouaziz.amine.18@gmail.com W: aminebouaziz.website

SOCIAL

Facebook: bouaziz.amine.18
Linkedin: Amine Bouaziz
Github: aminebouaziz

AMINE CHOKRI BOUAZIZ

ABOUT ME

I have an Italian nationality, I am a last year student, IEP-Sousse engineer in computer engineering.

I often work on freelance projects, I have one year experience as a full stack instructor in web development and most of all I am very passionate about sport.

Since I was 14 years old, I am active in community life, I belonged to several NGOs and during my university years I founded two clubs (ENACTUS and IEEE Student Branch)

EXPERIENCES

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Astrolab (Sousse, Tunisie) | August 2019 - Oct 2019

- Development of a human resource web application
- Technologies used for the backend: Nodejs | Express | Apollo | GraphQl | mongodb
- $\bullet \quad \mathsf{Technologies} \ \mathsf{used} \ \mathsf{for} \ \mathsf{the} \ \mathsf{frontend} \\ \mathsf{:} \ \mathsf{Reactjs}(\mathsf{Typescript}) \ | \ \mathsf{Apollo-client}$
- Agile method used: Scrum

EDTECH LEAD

GOMYCODE (Sousse, Tunisie) | June 2019 - Sept 2019

- Ensure daily meetings with instructors
- Provide technical interviews
- Postpone improvements based on student learning experience and instructor feedback.
- Manage the team of instructors.

FULL STACK INSTRUCTOR

GOMYCODE (Sousse, Tunisie) | August 2018 - Avril 2019

- Animate internal and external workshops.
- Ensure a good understanding of web development and different technologies
- Assessment of students

TOURISM REPRESENTATIVE

TUI italia | June 2017 - Oct 2017

- Responsible for information meetings for Italian clients.
- Ensure a good holiday for customers in Djerba, Tunisia.
- Management of arrivals and departures of customers.

EDUCATION

LYCÉE HAMMAM SOUSSE 1 | 2014 TECHNICAL BACCALAUREATE

EPI-Sousse, Tunise | 2015-2017 PREPARATORY CLASSES

EPI-Sousse, Tunise | depuis 2017 ENGINEERING COMPUTER SCIENCE

CERTIFICATION

NIVEAU 1 WEB DEVELOPMENT GOMYCODE| June 2018

NIVEAU 2 WEB DEVELOPMENT GOMYCODE| July 2018

3RD PLACE CPC-EPI ACPC| Mai 2018

Google Cloud platform (GCP) Essentials QWIKLABS| Janv 2019

PROJETS

Website for a pastry shop (E-commerce) reactjs | redux | nodejs | mongodb | express

Platform for articles synfony 4

Chatbot Rivescript | P5 | javascript

Inventory Management Application Java Swing & SQL

Good plans application IONIC & Firebase

Online Bookstore (E-commerce) Reactjs | firebase

LANGUES

ANGLAIS : intermediate

ARABE : Native
ITALIEN : Native
FRANÇAIS : Native